<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Burgers</string>
    <string name="country">Country</string>
    <string name="desc">Description</string>
    <string name="rating">Rating</string>
    <string name="Price">Price</string>
    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="share">Share</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="my_name">Achmad Faqih Suyudi</string>
    <string name="my_eamil">faqihsuyudi2020@gmail.com</string>

    <string-array name="data_img">
        <item>https://goldbelly.imgix.net/uploads/showcase_media_asset/image/137148/Gramercy-Tavern-Burger-and-Kielbasa-Kit-6.4.21-72ppi-1x1-15.jpg</item>
        <item>https://goldbelly.imgix.net/uploads/showcase_media_asset/image/134862/shake-shack-shackburger-8-pack.973a5e26836ea86d7e86a327becea2b0.png</item>
        <item>https://goldbelly.imgix.net/uploads/showcase_media_asset/image/132933/gotts-complete-cheeseburger-kit-for-4.7bdc74104b193427b3fe6eae39e05b5e.jpg</item>
        <item>https://goldbelly.imgix.net/uploads/showcase_media_asset/image/131436/le-big-matt-kit-for-6.1ddae6e382bb3218eeb0fd5247de115a.jpg</item>
        <item>https://goldbelly.imgix.net/uploads/showcase_media_asset/image/134022/shake-shack-shackburger-16-pack.316f8b09144db65931ea29e34869287a.png</item>
        <item>https://goldbelly.imgix.net/uploads/showcase_media_asset/image/107019/wagyu-burger-patties-12-pack.6116f4cd648dee20651f99e21e7d758b.jpg</item>
        <item>https://goldbelly.imgix.net/uploads/showcase_media_asset/image/133829/burger-bomb-kit-for-6.b0430200cfc153c1c15c7997236a6152.jpg</item>
        <item>https://goldbelly.imgix.net/uploads/showcase_media_asset/image/122768/handf-double-stack-burger-kit-for-4.4ee9f54b1d6087e9996335f07c13e5cd.jpg</item>
        <item>https://goldbelly.imgix.net/uploads/showcase_media_asset/image/66179/the-burger-bash-package.bd9d12d031865940bbe5faf15f1a62f8.jpg</item>

        <item>https://goldbelly.imgix.net/uploads/showcase_media_asset/image/105946/vegan-burger-grill-kit-for-4.1450ccef8c44f7394c93f58450ce67b9.jpg</item>
        <item>https://goldbelly.imgix.net/uploads/showcase_media_asset/image/114319/classic-juicy-lucy-burgers-sweet-potato-puffs-8-pack.36c8d716563c1af2d2ca1c1140d36273.jpg</item>
        <item>https://goldbelly.imgix.net/uploads/showcase_media_asset/image/133972/ribeye-burger-patties-6-pack.dd62bc3b8a096f15429571865ba5d561.jpg</item>
        <item>https://goldbelly.imgix.net/uploads/showcase_media_asset/image/133421/raouls-burgers-and-steaks-au-poivre-kit.aeafc64d55d6ad7274cb8ba1b562f8eb.jpg</item>
        <item>https://goldbelly.imgix.net/uploads/showcase_media_asset/image/129511/burger-fries-kit-for-4.ffc10e462cadece50d64f8ce5fd8ea7a.jpg</item>


    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_name">
        <item>Gramercy Tavern</item>
        <item>Shake Shack</item>
        <item>Gott\'s Roadside</item>
        <item>Emmy Squared</item>
        <item>Shake Shack</item>
        <item>Westholme Wagyu</item>
        <item>Old Homestead Steakhouse</item>
        <item>Holeman &amp; Finch</item>
        <item>Pat LaFrieda Meats</item>

        <item>Lekka Burger</item>
        <item>5–8 Club</item>
        <item>Rocker Bros. Meat &amp; Provisions</item>
        <item>Raoul\'s</item>
        <item>Rotier\'s Restaurant</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_desc">
        <item>The Gramercy Tavern Burger - 4 Pack</item>
        <item>Shake Shack ShackBurger® – 8 Pack</item>
        <item>Gott\'s Complete Cheeseburger Kit for 4</item>
        <item>Le Big Matt Burger Kit for 6</item>
        <item>Shake Shack Shackburger® – 16 Pack</item>
        <item>Wagyu Burger Patties - 12 Pack</item>
        <item>USDA Prime Burgers - Pack of 18 (8oz each)</item>
        <item>Burger Bomb Kit for 6</item>
        <item>Double Stack Burger Kit for 4</item>
        <item>Goldbelly Burger Bash Pack</item>

        <item>Vegan Burger Grill Kit for 4</item>
        <item>Classic Juicy Lucy Burgers - 8 Pack</item>
        <item>Brisket Burger - 8 Pack</item>
        <item>Raoul\'s Burgers and Steaks Au Poivre Kit</item>
        <item>Famous French Bread Burger + Fries Kit for 4</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_price">
        <item>99</item>
        <item>49</item>
        <item>99</item>
        <item>99</item>
        <item>89</item>
        <item>129</item>
        <item>129</item>
        <item>79</item>
        <item>109</item>

        <item>79</item>
        <item>149</item>
        <item>45</item>
        <item>249</item>
        <item>99</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_rate">
        <item>5</item>
        <item>5</item>
        <item>5</item>
        <item>5</item>
        <item>4</item>
        <item>5</item>
        <item>5</item>
        <item>4</item>
        <item>5</item>

        <item>4</item>
        <item>5</item>
        <item>4</item>
        <item>4</item>
        <item>4</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_country">
        <item>New York, NY</item>
        <item>New York, NY</item>
        <item>St. Helena, CA</item>
        <item>Brooklyn, NY</item>
        <item>New York, NY</item>
        <item>Queensland, Australia</item>
        <item>New York, NY</item>
        <item>Atlanta, GA</item>
        <item>North Bergen, NJ</item>

        <item>New York, NY</item>
        <item>Minneapolis, MN</item>
        <item>Los Angeles, CA</item>
        <item>New York, NY</item>
        <item>Nashville, TN</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_about">
        <item>Indulge in the deliciousness of Gramercy Tavern\'s famous burger with this 4-pack kit. Each kit contains everything you need to recreate the iconic burger experience at home. Whether you\'re hosting a backyard barbecue or enjoying a cozy dinner with family, these juicy burgers are sure to impress your taste buds.</item>
        <item>Enjoy Shake Shack\'s famous ShackBurger in the comfort of your home with this 8-pack. Made with high-quality ingredients, it\'s a must-try for burger enthusiasts. Whether you\'re celebrating a special occasion or just craving a delicious burger, these ShackBurgers® are sure to satisfy.</item>
        <item>Experience the flavors of Gott\'s Roadside with this complete cheeseburger kit for 4. Made with fresh ingredients and classic recipes, it\'s perfect for a family meal or gathering. Whether you\'re a cheeseburger aficionado or just looking for a tasty meal, this kit has everything you need to create delicious cheeseburgers at home.</item>
        <item>Treat yourself to Emmy Squared\'s famous Le Big Matt burger with this kit for 6. It\'s a mouthwatering combination of flavors that\'s sure to impress. Whether you\'re a burger connoisseur or just love trying new foods, this kit is perfect for sharing with friends or enjoying as a special treat.</item>
        <item>Upgrade your burger experience with this 16-pack of Shake Shack\'s famous ShackBurger®. Perfect for parties or stocking up for later, it\'s a crowd-pleaser. Whether you\'re hosting a backyard barbecue or planning a family dinner, these ShackBurgers® are sure to delight everyone at the table.</item>
        <item>Savor the rich flavors of Westholme Wagyu with these premium Wagyu burger patties. Made from the finest ingredients, they\'re perfect for grilling. Whether you\'re a meat lover or just enjoy gourmet food, these Wagyu burger patties are sure to impress.</item>
        <item>Experience burger bliss with this Burger Bomb Kit for 6 from Old Homestead Steakhouse. Each kit contains all the fixings for a mouthwatering burger experience that\'ll leave you craving more. Whether you\'re celebrating a special occasion or just looking to elevate your burger game, this kit has everything you need.</item>
        <item>Get ready for a flavor explosion with Holeman &amp; Finch\'s Double Stack Burger Kit for 4. With premium ingredients and delicious flavors, it\'s perfect for a cozy night in or a backyard barbecue. Whether you\'re cooking for friends or family, this kit is sure to impress.</item>
        <item>Join the burger bash with Pat LaFrieda Meats\' Goldbelly Burger Bash Pack. Packed with flavor and ready to impress, it\'s the ultimate burger experience delivered right to your door. Whether you\'re hosting a party or just looking for a delicious meal, this pack has everything you need to satisfy your burger cravings.</item>



        <item>Lekka Burger offers a delightful vegan burger grill kit for four. Crafted with a combination of plant-based ingredients, these burgers are perfect for those seeking a delicious and cruelty-free meal. Whether you\'re a vegan enthusiast or simply looking to explore new flavors, this kit promises a satisfying dining experience.</item>
        <item>Indulge in the classic Juicy Lucy burgers along with delectable sweet potato puffs, all in an 8-pack kit from 5-8 Club. These iconic burgers, oozing with cheese and flavor, paired with crispy sweet potato puffs, are a delight for any burger lover. Whether you\'re hosting a gathering or craving a satisfying meal, this kit is sure to impress.</item>
        <item>Rocker Bros. Meat &amp; Provisions offers a gourmet experience with their ribeye burger patties. Crafted from premium ribeye cuts, these patties are rich in flavor and offer a juicy bite with every bite. Whether you\'re grilling for friends or enjoying a meal with loved ones, these ribeye burger patties are sure to impress.</item>
        <item>Raoul\'s presents their indulgent Burgers and Steaks Au Poivre kit, offering a culinary delight for steak and burger lovers alike. Made with premium ingredients and seasoned to perfection, these burgers and steaks promise a gourmet dining experience. Whether you\'re celebrating a special occasion or simply craving a luxurious meal, this kit is sure to satisfy.</item>
        <item>Experience the iconic flavors of Rotier\'s Restaurant with their famous French bread burger and fries kit for four. Made with fresh ingredients and classic recipes, these burgers offer a delightful combination of flavors and textures. Whether you\'re hosting a gathering or simply craving a delicious meal, this kit promises a memorable dining experience.</item>



    </string-array>


</resources>